THE CHARACTERS, INSTITUTIONS,
COMPANIES, AND PLACES
DEPICTED IN THIS DRAMA
ARE ENTIRELY FICTIONAL
Mr. Yu…
You're handsome.
Yu Eun-ho.
EPISODE 5
Gosh, my head.
What? Was that a dream?
No way. Seriously?
No, it must be a dream.
Did you go back home in the morning?
Honestly,
why do you crawl back
to the office after drinking?
Now that we're old,
sleeping on the couch hurts the back.
Your back doesn't deserve
to suffer like that.
Mi-ae, did everyone get home
safely last night?
Yes, I sent everyone home.
- Including Mr. Yu?
- Yes.
He was looking for you,
so I told him not to worry and go home
since you'll be in the office.
Why?
Nothing.
Give me five minutes.
Was it really a dream?
What did you say?
It's nothing.
Goodness.
KANG JI-YUN
You have the international
recruitment association seminar at 12 p.m.
You have the final interview
with The Economy Herald at 3 p.m.
Mr. Yu?
After the company party yesterday,
you didn't return
to the office?
No.
I didn't return here.
All right.
You may go.
I'll bring the documents
for the interview.
Hello, sir.
Okay.
It disappeared.
Pardon?
Oh, it's nothing.
Yes, I just finished the meeting.
Yes.
Yuseon Apparel is looking for a director
to lead their international sales.
Before entering the international market,
they plan to consolidate their teams
to establish a global business department.
I'm making a list of candidates
in high positions who made
significant results globally
during the last five years.
Gosh.
A bug.
Is there a bug?
There's a bug?
Yes, sir?
Yes, I'm aware of it.
Isn't his nose just a work of art?
Right.
Do you like this idol group too?
You agreed it was a work of art…
Yeah, what a piece of art.
That's surprising.
You don't need to join me.
I'm getting off work
directly from the meeting.
I'll take you there.
I'm going there alone, okay? Alone.
Ms. Kang?
Careful, you might fall.
You asked for these documents.
DREAMS AND NIGHTMARES
DREAMS: THE SCIENCE
OF UNLOCKING OUR INNER REALITY
THE SIXTH SLEEP
NEIGHBORHOOD BOOK STORE MAP
Most dreams that we remember
and talk about
seem like they took place in reality.
If not, we usually forget about them.
Hi, old lady.
Kiddo, you come here often.
I'm not a kiddo.
I'm not an old lady either.
What are you reading today?
It's about a new ice cream shop
in the snowman village.
There's a lot of delicious ice cream.
You must like ice cream.
Which is your favorite?
- Mint chocolate.
- You have good taste.
Do you like mint chocolate too?
Yes.
I'm not interested in food,
but I like mint chocolate milk.
Have you tried mint chocolate candy?
How about mint chocolate cookies?
Oh, right.
There's new mint chocolate bread.
Have you tried it?
Are there that many types?
So you haven't tried it?
They sell it at the supermarket.
Want to go with me?
Are you allowed to go?
By the way, where's your mom?
Uncle, can I go to the supermarket
with this lady?
What?
Sure, do you want to?
THREE-WAY SUPERMARKET
What do you think? Isn't it tasty?
It's good.
Help yourself.
You shouldn't ask just anyone
to come with you.
It's not just anyone.
I don't ask just anyone to come with me.
Then?
It's because I like you, sis.
You like me?
You just called me "sis."
Why? You don't like it?
What's your name?
I'm Byeol, seven years old.
Byeol, you're only seven,
but you have a good eye for people.
You can call me "sis."
Did you know that Byeol
and Ms. Kang got close to each other?
Byeol?
- Eun-ho's daughter?
- Yes.
They even went
to the supermarket together.
By the way,
it felt strange to see them together.
Goodness.
There's nothing strange about it.
What are you trying to imagine?
They get along as coworkers.
Don't try to tie them together.
I just thought…
You never know.
Aren't you going to work?
I want to go home.
Can't we even talk about it?
Ji-yun's too good for him.
Kwang-hee.
Goodness, you startled me.
You really did.
Nice going.
Take a look around.
Everyone else is working hard.
You're the only one dozing off.
I only slept three hours last night.
I had to wait in line early
to make a purchase this morning.
Did you sleep well?
Kwang-hee, when I was your age,
I saved every penny to buy a house.
What on earth is this?
Obsessing over dressing up
with luxury brands--
I dress up using the money I earn.
Oh, my.
That briefcase is really hard to get.
Who is that with a discerning eye?
Nice to meet you.
Oh, that person…
Who is he?
Come on, Mr. Kim.
He's the CEO of an online luxury brand
platform that's hot these days.
CEO Jin Sung-ho of Deluxe Line.
Oh, a luxury brand platform?
What is that anyway?
You can buy and sell luxury brands online.
You know that, right?
Of course, I do. A luxury brand platform.
So, what position does he need?
You're looking for
a luxury brand appraiser?
There's more demand
as the market increased,
but there are
only a few certified experts.
When I find someone competent,
a competitor snatches him away.
When I find someone certified, he
has one or two years of work experience.
It's almost impossible
to find an appraiser.
It's not surprising
that appraisers are rare.
The appraisal skills determine
the platform's credibility.
As we handle highly priced products,
when you make one mistake,
your credibility plummets.
That's why
I need an appraiser in charge
who can represent my platform.
Someone who trains appraisers.
An expert who evaluates
the final appraisal.
It's all about competence.
Competence is all I'm looking for.
We're the only headhunter, and they're
willing to negotiate the income.
As long as we find a good candidate,
they're willing to adjust the conditions.
Isn't the company size too small for us?
Is this really necessary?
They're preparing
an in-house examination center.
If we're successful, we'll be in charge
of hiring employees at the center.
Then it isn't a bad deal.
In that case…
He would be happy to take it.
Right?
He's an expert in that field.
What's going on?
Am I the only one out of the loop?
Who?
Who's going to take it?
Who is it?
Kwang-hee.
- Me?
- Yes.
Consultant Kim Kwang-hee from Team Two?
Consultant Lee Kwang-hee from Team One.
Yes, Lee Kwang-hee.
Excuse me.
What is it, Ms. Seo?
What is it?
NURI DREAM PUBLISHING COMPANY
Mr. Woo, I'll be counting on you.
Please work hard on it.
I'm still not sure about hiring someone
during this recession.
Instead of reducing the supply
during hard times, you should increase it.
When you supply books of good quality,
the demand will increase.
That's why even when I couldn't get paid,
I didn't stop publishing books.
That title sounds interesting.
Rainbow Bingsu?
Gosh, that's another amazing book,
but books like this don't sell.
The writer is such a nice person.
My editor tries really hard,
but the first edition hasn't sold out yet.
The writer looks so discouraged.
Yes, thank you for your concern.
Take care.
Thank you.
Ms. Jung, stay strong.
- Let's make your new book successful.
- Okay.
- We can do it.
Ms. Jung, I wish you luck too.
JUNG SU-HYEON
Mr. Woo, do you know our writer, Ms. Jung?
Weren't you the one
who called me Father last time?
Right?
Hello.
What a small world.
So you're a writer.
As you're full of imagination,
you thought I was a dad.
I apologize.
- How do you write picture books?
- Oh my.
Pardon?
Do you get ideas easily
like surging water?
Do you get inspired?
- I dig a hole.
- What?
I concentrate hard for hours
tugging at my hair
to come up with ideas.
The pain of creation.
You can still write a few more books.
You still have lots of hair.
Can I get your autograph?
I like to make investments early.
I'll make use of it
when your book becomes a bestseller.
What's your name?
It's Woo Jeong-hoon.
Woo Jeong-hoon…
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
- Goodbye, then.
- Bye.
Ms. Jung!
The pain of creation, you can do it!
- I can do it.
- You can do it.
Invest wisely.
Where are we on the luxury brand
appraiser candidates?
I made a long list
and shared it with the HR at Deluxe Line.
Currently, we have a total
of three candidates.
An employee at the customs
who only picks out the counterfeit.
The logo is a bit off.
The stitches are defective.
This part is wrong.
The label is defective.
Recently starred on Genuine or Fake,
a rising star appraiser who distinguished
the genuine article five times in a row.
I can distinguish between
the genuine and the counterfeit.
A duty-free shop manager of 20 years
at a top 10 luxury brand shop.
Okay, not too bad.
Proceed the meeting quickly
so the competitors don't hire them.
I will start by meeting the candidate
whom the client wants the most, Ms. Kang.
Min-seok.
- Hello.
Oh, here you go.
- Have a seat.
- Okay.
ASSISTANT JUNIOR OFFICIAL
KANG MIN-SEOK
Hello, everyone! Ciao, hi, aloha.
What's going on here?
This feels like déjà vu.
What's with the vibe?
Why is it so down this morning…
What?
Even my lines are the same.
Kyung-hwa, what's wrong?
What's going on today?
The number one candidate
whom Deluxe Line wanted.
Today is his first day
at one of the competitors.
Whose work was it?
Career Way.
CEO Kim Hye-jin?
Mr. Kang Min-seok started work today
at Luxury Seller.
You seem used to the work already.
This is all thanks to you.
Please let me handle everything
related to Peoplez.
After all, I owe them.
I don't work with underqualified people.
I won't be seeing you again.
Not here, nor any other search firms.
I need you to explain
why we lost our candidate
to Career Way.
Didn't we contact him first?
The candidate needed more time--
You weren't aware that he was
in contact with another?
If the candidate is indecisive,
shouldn't you know
if he doesn't like the offer
or he's comparing us
with other headhunters?
What about replacing candidates?
Well, I've contacted a few,
but I haven't found anyone
who fits the description.
I need to start searching again…
Have you been waiting
for the candidate to decide?
Without any plan B?
Kwang-hee has a meeting with
the business team at Deluxe Line today.
Before the meeting,
it'd be good if you update them
on what's going on.
Get me a meeting with CEO Jin.
Is this a joke?
You told me that I could count on you,
but the result is losing the candidate
to a competitor?
I apologize.
It is my fault.
During the remaining period,
we'll find a better candidate.
I'm sorry, Ms. Kang.
There's no need to be sorry.
Find a new candidate
within the time period.
The client won't be satisfied
with our second best.
Find a more qualified candidate
than before and prove your skills.
What if I can't prove my skills…
When you lost the candidate
that the client wanted,
didn't you brace yourself?
Didn't you?
Yes.
I'll get fired if I can't find anyone.
Mr. Yu, please follow up on this project.
Eun-ho…
Hello, this is the search firm Peoplez.
Hello, sir.
About the designer you wanted to
recommend last time…
I'm calling you about your CV.
You work in street brands now?
Did you work in quality control at Pigaro?
Are you certified as an appraiser?
Yes!
How long have you been certified?
A year and a half?
I'll contact you again later.
Okay.
I called them all.
Mr. Kim, aren't you hungry?
- Shall I go and buy some bread?
- Bread sounds good.
Kwang-hee.
Would you like to come?
What if I get fired like this?
I have no solution.
I think the order is wrong.
There's time to worry later
after finding a candidate.
You aren't saying that I won't get fired.
Gosh, I'm choking up on bread.
Anyway, just where am I supposed to
find a candidate?
I looked through all my lists,
but I can't find the right one.
There isn't any.
DAEGIL MOTORS
They probably know everything about cars.
What?
It's needless to say
because they're experts.
Competent mechanics recognize problems
just by listening to the sound of the car.
They even distinguish models
by the engine sounds alone.
That would be the case for masters.
They've worked on so many cars.
Why do you keep changing the subject?
We're talking about
luxury brand appraisers…
When you've worked on
many luxury brand products…
I got goose bumps.
They would know instinctively.
What's real and what's fake.
I should make a new list
of candidates with expert repairers.
Let's start the search
with luxury brand repairers.
They must know repairing experts.
Online luxury brand communities.
There will be information
on hidden experts on social media.
Are you going to approach
luxury brand repairers?
The candidates on the existing database
have already been exposed to our clients.
They won't be good enough,
so I came up with this idea.
I can change it, if you'd like.
A luxury brand repair expert?
That's a good direction.
The veteran whom CEO Jin is looking for
could be hiding among them.
Good luck on your search.
Yes, Ms. Kang.
I'll make sure to find a good candidate.
You may go.
- Well done.
- You worked hard.
- Good job today.
- Thank you for your work.
Good work, all.
Eun-ho.
Thanks.
I'll go over it
before handing it to Ms. Kang.
- Head home.
- Thank you, Eun-ho.
Go ahead.
Good work.
Why is this here?
Ms. Kang.
Ms. Kang?
Mr. Yu…
It wasn't a dream.
Ms. Kang, if you're working longer,
shall I order food…
Ms. Kang?
There you are.
Are you okay? It's still chilly at night.
That day,
you returned to the office, didn't you?
This.
It was on the floor of my office.
On the day of our company party,
weren't you with me
in the office?
Yes.
Why did you pretend not to remember?
How much do you remember?
How much do you want me to remember?
Let's say that it didn't happen.
Just like now.
Okay.
Then I will remember it just like now.
Dad.
How much do you want me to remember?
Let's say that it didn't happen.
Just like now.
How much do you remember?
How much do you want me to remember?
Let's say that it didn't happen.
Just like now.
Okay.
Then I will remember it just like now.
DO YOU LIKE BRAHMS?
Eun-ho, over here.
A tasty twisted doughnut place.
Can I get another twisted doughnut?
- Did you find it?
- Yes.
I saw the Garim Repairing employees
go in with things to repair.
In the luxury brand repairing industry,
Garim Repairing is considered the best.
The master that the owner of Garim
Repairing kept as a secret. Exactly.
They're in this market.
Good job. So, where is this person?
About that,
I need to look for them now.
Me and you.
We have to look everywhere here.
The market looks
nice but big.
Has it always been this big?
Thank you.
I'm not sure.
Okay, thank you.
I haven't seen this
since I opened my shop.
- You haven't seen it?
- No.
I see. Have a good day.
- I don't know about that.
- Okay.
- How about this?
- Thank you.
It looks great on you.
How about a gift for your mother?
- Thank you.
- It's quite nice.
The market is big, but they're not here.
Thank you for everything.
I think that I'm done here.
- Yes?
- Can I get some tteokbokki and fish cakes?
Are you replacing your meal
with snacks again?
You should eat a proper meal.
Many people need my help again today.
One moment.
- Here you go.
- Okay.
- Good luck with business.
- See you.
I think I missed one.
This is called Good Lifestyle--
- Ma'am.
- Yes?
What kind of work does she do?
She repairs bags.
Let's see.
- Thank you.
- Goodness.
- Have a good day.
Wait, you gave me too much.
She was here.
She was definitely here.
Eun-ho.
This alley wasn't on the map.
You're right.
Eun-ho, say something.
You need to direct me so that I can…
REPAIR REQUEST
Didn't we find the right place?
Yes.
Unbelievable.
You startled me.
When did you get in?
Are you here for a repair?
Hello.
How did you do this?
It became a new wallet.
My client left it with me with trust.
I should keep it clean.
The backstitches aren't consistent.
It must be precious to him
because he gets it repaired.
How do you know that?
It's what I do all day long.
It'd be strange if I didn't know.
Each brand and product has
its unique way of backstitching.
You know that it's different
for each brand and product.
GARIM REPAIRING
Kwang-hee, that's…
I found it. This is it.
Ma'am, do you happen to
work with Garim Repairing?
Yes.
I also repair all of their items.
Ma'am, goodness!
- I'm sorry.
- Eun-ho, this is so…
- Your workplace is practically hidden.
- That's…
How could we find you?
Pearls are always found in the deep sea.
- That's loud.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- Ma'am.
- I'm sorry.
- We're from Peoplez.
- That's right.
What?
Ms. Cho Young-sook.
She learned how to repair
at the age of 17.
She's been doing it for 37 years.
She's an expert in luxury brand repair.
Including the material's color, thickness,
shape, and number of stitches,
she can make it exactly
like the real thing.
With years of experience
in repairing luxury brand goods,
she can distinguish counterfeits
instinctively at her fingertips.
In other words,
she has long, bona fide experience.
Leyard Shoulder Bag, Kilin Mini Tote Bag,
and Haegas Belt.
Yes, Leyard.
Kilin. My goodness.
Gosh.
Haegas Belt.
Eun-ho, this is amazing.
You're exactly right.
You're a master.
A person like me at a company?
I only graduated from elementary school.
Your educational background
isn't important.
We're making this offer
based on your competence.
Thank you for the offer,
but Eun-ho, I don't feel comfortable.
You don't need to feel uncomfortable.
Think of it as continuing the same work
that you love doing.
I don't understand why.
There are many who are certified,
and there are many who studied a lot.
All I did was sew work.
All I did was sew, glue, and cut
every day.
At some point,
I naturally figured out
what's genuine and what's fake.
Your time spent.
You should be treated accordingly
for the time you spent
naturally gaining that knowledge.
Don't underestimate
the value of your time spent.
Your hands that have worked
for a long time.
They must find it unfair.
Ma'am,
your hands are very special.
It won't be late to refuse
after thinking about it.
We'll be waiting for your call.
KANG JI-YUN, PEOPLEZ
Dad, where's Ttosoon?
- And Gom?
- In the second drawer for toys.
Dad, what about my pajamas?
The nightstand next to your bed?
Not these.
My pajamas with teddy bears.
Those are too thin for now.
Aren't you taking this too?
Why do you look so happy?
Are you that excited to sleep
with your kindergarten friends?
You're making me sad.
Will you be able to sleep well without me?
Dad.
You should be independent now.
I can't be the love of your life.
Get yourself a girlfriend and go on dates.
It's TGIF.
TGIF? Where did you learn that?
Dad, I'm seven years old.
TG…
Be careful.
HANEUL KINDERGARTEN
How can they be so excited?
They're practically flying.
Jung Seo-jun woke up at six this morning.
- He did?
- Yes.
I feel betrayed by Seo-jun.
I know. I'm disappointed.
Children at Haneul Kindergarten.
Can you sleep
without your parents tonight?
- Yes!
Say goodbye to your mom and dad.
Go on.
- Eat.
- A lot of good food.
I love you, Byeol.
Mom, sleep with this if you get scared.
He'll protect you.
Thanks you, my son.
See you tomorrow, Dad.
Take care of Byeol.
- Okay.
- Bye.
Everyone, let's go inside.
- Okay.
Line up and go in.
Go inside.
HANEUL KINDERGARTEN
Moms and dads.
You're free tonight!
Enjoy yourselves!
- Ms. Seo.
- Hey.
Eun-ho.
I heard that you're free tonight
after a long time.
How did you know?
- Did Kang-seok tell you?
- Yes.
A Friday without kids.
Isn't this huge? It only happens
a few times in a year.
Do you have plans?
I do.
Gosh, what is it?
Getting documents ready
for Ms. Kang's lecture.
Her upcoming lecture is very--
What's wrong with you?
Have you become a workaholic like her
now that you work as her secretary?
What happened to our employees?
Ji-yun must be the problem.
I won't stand for this. Tonight,
all of you should come to my house.
So… Hey, Mr. Woo.
You have no plans tonight, right?
Even if you do, come to my house.
I'll treat the board of directors tonight.
All of a sudden?
Ms. Kang has been sensitive these days.
I meant to invite her over
and make her food.
Let's eat together.
But you're a bad cook.
I've never had braised ribs
like yours before.
You should change the name
to braised rocks.
There's delivery food.
I can order what you want to eat
and treat you well.
Then come to my house.
- I'll treat you.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Is that okay?
- Yes, please come.
- Then I'd be so grateful.
Eun-ho's cooking is amazing.
Last time, I went to his house
and fell in love with his cooking.
Can we really come?
Please come.
Okay, let's meet at Eun-ho's place.
Everyone is required to come.
You'll be there, right?
Well, I…
Is Ms. Kang going?
She'd never go
to the house of an employee.
But it's Eun-ho's. I'll persuade her.
What's so different about Mr. Yu's house?
Anyway, it's up to you.
Why is he being so fussy?
I sent you the address.
Come to Eun-ho's house by 7 p.m.
I'm not going.
Why not? Let's go.
We can have delicious food,
drink wine, and have fun.
We don't have time for that.
Besides, why would I go to Mr. Yu's house?
You still have to eat.
It's a board of directors meeting.
Why at that place?
Mi-ae, that's a nuisance.
Not going when invited is
more of a nuisance.
If you get that,
just come with a delicious cake.
No, I'm not going.
I made myself clear.
Don't wait for me.
That would be your loss.
I made myself clear
that his cooking is amazing.
She's as stubborn as a mule.
I'll call you back after checking
Ms. Kang's schedule.
Talk to you soon.
Make all the afternoon schedule
happen in one place.
Go and meet Ms. Cho with Kwang-hee.
Yes, ma'am.
The fact that she called us means
that she's considering it.
Please persuade her in person.
Understand what her concerns are.
If there are conditions she wants--
Ms. Kang.
Don't worry so much.
She'll be persuaded.
It's the right position for Ms. Cho.
It will come to a decision in a week,
whatever it may be.
You may get off work from there.
Okay.
Are you also coming tonight?
No, I'm not going.
Please come.
I'd like to make
a home-cooked meal for you.
I'll get going.
As you can see,
the demand continues to increase.
There will be more
during the second half of the year.
As you may already know,
headhunting is especially important
for product buyers.
We will consider what's important…
Please take a careful look
and let us know.
Please come.
I'd like to make
a home-cooked meal for you.
What's so special about food?
DEAR MR. DELIVERY MAN,
PLEASE HELP YOURSELF, THANK YOU
Sure…
it's just a group dinner.
Ms. Kang?
Sorry, I ran a bit late.
Is no one else here?
It got canceled because no one could come.
A notice was sent in the group chat…
You aren't in the group chat.
MI-AE
Where are you? What's this?
Why didn't you come?
Because of you--
Ms. Kang.
Yes?
Would you like to have dinner?
No, I only stopped by.
I happened to be in the neighborhood.
I also happened to find this on the way.
I mean, I was just in the neighborhood.
- And--
- Thank you.
I bought all the ingredients.
I was bummed out when it got canceled.
Do you like bean paste stew?
Are you uncomfortable?
No.
Just give me a moment.
I'll make it with care.
Do it carelessly.
Carelessly…
YELLOW PRINCESS
What the heck?
It turn off on its own
if you leave it alone.
There, it's off.
What is Byeol's dad doing tonight?
Call him instead of waiting.
I wasn't waiting for him.
You're free from kids tonight.
Go out to the movies.
What was that? Chimaek?
Have some fried chicken and beer.
I didn't know you knew things like that.
That's not all.
If you hesitate too long, you'll lose him.
What if he invites someone home
and cooks for her?
It's game over
once she tastes his bean paste stew.
Aren't you embarrassed to say that?
And how about that broad back of his
when he's cooking?
Here you go.
Try it.
I finally got to make you
a home-cooked meal.
That darn home-cooked meal.
What?
Did you put something in it?
Did you really make all of this?
I think I told you that I'm a good cook.
I think you're better as a cook.
Then make a reservation next time.
It's good to see you eat so well.
How pretty.
I admit that it was delicious.
Since when did you start cooking?
It's been 30 years.
This is my survival skill
I honed for 30 years.
I make one compliment
and you get ahead of yourself.
I know how old you are.
It's true.
Then have you been living alone
since you were in elementary school?
I grew up well, didn't I?
You did.
Well done.
You too, Ms. Kang.
What's this?
You did an excellent job.
A compliment should be done properly.
YOU DID AN EXCELLENT JOB
Excuse me, Ms. Kang. I have to take this.
I finished eating, so I'll get going.
You should stay for the cake.
Please wait a minute.
But…
Did you have fun?
Did you have dinner?
Are you sleeping in a tent?
Isn't it chilly at night?
Of course, I'm thinking a lot about you.
Dress warmly, okay?
How did you spend your day today?
I did tons of stuff.
We played Cowboys and Indians, soccer,
and even a snack game.
Right, we also did treasure hunting.
I found two pieces of treasure, Dad.
Byeol, that's impressive.
Your teacher prepared a lot.
Yes, it was really fun.
Is that why you didn't think
about me today?
To be honest, I didn't really.
Are you disappointed?
No.
I prefer that you have fun.
I'll think more about you.
Dad, I have to go.
Other kids have to call home too.
Good night, Dad.
You too. I love you.
Bye.
Ms. Kang, sorry for making you wait…
- What's going on?
- What?
What the heck?
What do you mean?
- The sun is up.
- What?
- What time is it?
- What time is it now?
What's going on here?
What am I doing here?
Dad, get yourself a girlfriend
and go on dates.
It's TGIF.
- You have to go now.
- Where?
- She's on her way.
- Who?
- My daughter!
- Your daughter.
What? Your daughter?
Goodness.
My bag!
Your bag? I'll get it.
- And my cell phone.
- Your cell phone?
What time is it?
Snap out of it.
The elevator.
Why did you sleep in?
You didn't set an alarm?
I did, but…
By the way, did we do anything?
Pardon?
We didn't even hold hands.
All we did was eat and sleep--
Is it good, Byeol?
Dad.
Byeol.
No.
Stop it.
Don't go.
No.
It's all right.
It's okay.
Let me ask you one thing.
- Why did you kick me out?
- Why did you run away?
- Exactly.
Are you saying that
we've been selling counterfeits?
What happens if her appraisal is wrong?
Who would even believe me?
Everyone says that I'm wrong.
The kiddo who comes often
to the book store.
Is that Mr. Yu's daughter?
- Kitty!
- Byeol!
Eun-ho, did something happen to Byeol?
- Are you okay?
- Actually, I'm not sure.
You're doing well now.
I'm sure that Byeol knows.
That her dad is making an effort.
What kind of person is Yu Eun-ho to you?
I'm doomed.
Subtitle translation by: Helena Noh